[{"answer": "If I lose my temper, you're totalled man", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Totally", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "See you're afraid that they won't take you.  You don't belong so you just have to dump all over it..", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Well you wouldn't know...You don't even know any of us", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well...it wouldn't have anything to do with you activities people being assholes...now would it", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well, I don't know any lepers either, but I'm not gonna run out and join one of their fucking clubs", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Oh, I know...I feel all empty inside because of it.  I have such a deep admiration for guys that roll around on the floor with other guys", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, but I do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You get along with your parents", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You're an idiot anyway...But if you say you get along with your parents well you're a liar too", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "K", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Nooo...It's a fat girl's name", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Allright girls, that's thirty minutes for lunch..", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Here..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Here..", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well, I don't care what you think, my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What are you talking about", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No!  Drop what, what're you talking about", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What's that", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Sushi", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, the activities hall", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No you don't know what you're talking about", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Don't you wanna hear my excuse", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I'm thinking of trying out for a scholarship", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Whether or not, I wanna hang out with them..", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Do you", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Are you gonna be like a shopping bag lady?  You know like, sit in alleyways and like talk to buildings and wear men's shoes and that kinda thing", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Why do you have to do anything", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Where do you want me to go", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Go away..", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "GO away", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Do you have any idea how completely gross that is", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "First few times?  You mean he did it more than once", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Have you ever done it", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Have you ever done it with a normal person", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Look, I'm not gonna discuss my private life with total strangers", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "A what", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Not the only difference, I hope", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I'm not a tease", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No, I never said that, she twisted my words around", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I don't use it period", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " That was you", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yeah, I know him..", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Why'd you think it'd be easy", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I take shop...you must be a fuckin' idiot", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I take shop...you must be a fuckin' idiot", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "No, you're a genius because you can't make a lamp..", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I wanna see what my friend can do", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Now, everybody can do something..", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I can't do anything", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "There's one thing I can do, no forget it, it's way too embarrassing", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Not me...ever..", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "What happens", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yeah..", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Yeah, I want the truth..", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Well if you did", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I just wanna tell, each of you, that I wouldn't do that...I wouldn't and I will not!  'Cause I think that's real shitty..", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well I didn't do it, did I?  No, I don't think so", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "No, it was a flare gun, went off in my locker", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "True, but I think we'd all kinda say the same thing", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "True, but, you're the smartest, right", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Were you really disgusted about what I did with my lipstick", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Truth..", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Nothing's wrong, it's just so different.  I can see your face", "docId": "Breakfast-Club_-The.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " It's good", "qsentId": 66}]